Luigi Tejada

Full Stack Software Engineer

Brooklyn, NY | luigitejada@yahoo.com | GitHub | LinkedIn

Brand Statement:

Software Engineer with 4+ years of customer service experiences allowing for an increase in customer satisfaction through communication and understanding. Knowledge of implementing plans for optimizing service, quality, and efficiency. Passion for learning new technologies and techniques for surpassing expectations.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: Express.js, Mongoose

Databases: MongoDBTools: Git, GitHub, VSCode

EDUCATION

General Assembly | Software Engineering Immersive | Remote

Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems | New York City College of Technology | NYC

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Immersive | General Assembly | Remote | August 2022 – November 2022 Successfully completed 500+ hours of expert led instruction in Software Engineering and hands-on learning of Full-Stack fundamentals and the industry's most in demand technologies. Developed projects, including:

- Wordle: Built with Javascript primarily, with HTML and CSS [Wordle repo] [Wordle site]
- Tic-Tac-Toe: Built with HTML and Javascript [<u>Tic-Tac-Toe repo</u>] [<u>Tic-Tac-Toe site</u>]
- PizzaPanda: Built with Node.js, MongoDB, Javascript, HTML, and CSS [PizzaPanda repo] [PizzaPanda site]
- Filmingo Fantasy Film Making: Built with React, MongoDB, CSS [Filmingo repo] [Filmingo site]

Produce Order Writer Specialist | Whole Foods Market | Brooklyn, NY | October 2020–June 2021

- Ordered, replenished, and merchandised produce and participated in regional programs for purchasing and promotions.
- Monitored inventory control and replenished product based upon WFM ordering standards.
- Assisted in organizing and developing promotional displays and maintaining Order-To-Shelf standards.
- Purchased and replenished produce through proper buying procedures.
- Completed spoilage, sampling, temperature, sweep worksheets, and participated in inventory required.
- Maximized sales potential through effective and proper procedures for stocking and merchandising products.
- Ensured orders for product are timely and accurate to monitor inventory turns.
- Analyzed and controlled product transfers, waste, and spoilage.
- Maximized sales potential through effective and proper procedures for prepping, storing, rotating, stocking, and merchandising product.
- Followed and complied, or ensured compliance, with established procedures, including Weights and Measures, health and sanitation, and safe work practices.

Produce Team Member | Whole Foods Market | New York City | August 2018 – September 2020

- Ensured a fresh and appealing display by keeping cases and shelves clean and well stocked by front-facing, checking codes, rotating, and removing out-of-date products to ensure maximum sales potential.
- Provided excellent customer service and address needs of customers in a timely and effective manner.
- Maintained and ensured accuracy of signs and pricing including but not limited to the produce department.
- Maintained a safe, clean and well-organized working and shopping environment with established procedures according to health and sanitation and safe work practices.
- Followed and complied with all applicable health and sanitation procedures and adhere to safe work practices.
- Operated and sanitized all equipment in a safe and proper manner.

Fulfillment Associate | Amazon | New York City | July 2017 – January 2019

- Performed production duties as needed such as pick/pack orders at an average of 95 units per hour for a 10-hour shift. Thus resulting in pick/packing 25% (average 4,000 units) of the sites daily orders.
- Receive/stow product, ensure inventory accuracy, and unload/load trucks.
- Coordinated physical and virtual workflows to ensure products are shipped on time to meet customer delivery promise.
- Troubleshot problems through to resolution, escalating to Area Manager as necessary.
- Assisted Area Manager in daily management of department/FC duties including training and communicating with internal and external suppliers.